<resources>
    <string name="btn">Go</string>
    <string name="title">Porscheist</string>
    <string name="app_name">Porscheist</string>
    <string name="activity2_name">Porsche</string>
    <string name="porsche">porsche</string>
    <string name="singer">The final product, a Porsche 911 “reimagined” by Singer, leaves no detail unattended. A new engine, drivetrain, and suspension increase the driving performance, while painstakingly refurbished bodywork and Singer touches like handwoven door panels and quilted leather trunk liners let you know this is a very special car. \n\n

After contracting with Singer, customers turn over their “964”-model Porsche 911 (built between 1989 and 1994) and a sizable deposit before the company puts 4,000 hours into restoring, tuning, and customizing it. \n\n

Singer Vehicle Design’s basic restoration services begin at $395,000 but average $600,000, “which is still way too cheap,” says Dickinson, “for the assiduous labor and hand-built parts required.” (He does, however, hold a “deep-seated English guilt” over the steep price tag.) \n\n

In 2009, Dickinson charged one of his first customers $300,000 and ended up spending $800,000 on the restoration. “I picked a number out of thin air and of course it was nowhere near, and we’ve spent the last eight years really understanding how astronomically expensive it is to do this,” he says, reclining in his unofficial uniform of a black T-shirt, cuffed jeans, sneakers, and a jaunty green Goorin Bros. cap. \n\n

The former rock star restoring six-figure Porsches recalls a car-­obsessed childhood underpinned by a curiosity about mechanical objects, heritage brands, and the trappings of the retro international man of mystery: sunglasses, cigarettes, and watches. (The company entered the watch market this summer, launching the $41,000 Singer Track 1 chronograph with Swiss designer Marco Borraccino.) Dickinson’s earliest automotive memory: watching the friendly face and businesslike rear of a green Porsche 911 pass his family’s VW Beetle on a summer vacation in France when he was 5. Ever since, Dickinson says, he’s “had a fascination with the ultimate version of things.” \n\n

</string>
    <string name="gemballa">It’s not out of the ordinary for aftermarket tuners to take on Porsche’s most sought-after platforms — after all, the Stuttgart-born company has built its entire catalog around race-ready performance, helping to bridge the gap between intimidating horsepower and everyday driving. Gemballa, one of the country’s premier Porsche tuning shops, has solicited the manufacturer’s legendary Carrera GT for yet another mindblowing build — this time, taking more than 1,000 man-hours to complete. \n\n

The “Mirage GT” represented here is a mysterious beast — not much is known surrounding its story or details. But the German tuner wasn’t shy about revealing the performance figures for the one-off wonder, which boasts an astounding 661 horsepower (58 horsepower more than standard), and 465 lb-ft of torque, enhanced from an already impressive 435 lb-ft. The vehicle’s naturally-aspirated 5.7-liter engine provides a pronounced note that’s specific to the analog supercar, alongside a newly introduced catalytic converter setup, stainless steel exhaust system, and custom air intake. An ECU remap helps to even out the Carrera’s performance, accelerating the vehicle from 0-62 in just 3.7 seconds, while on the supercar’s top end, the 205-MPH top speed provides all of the exhilarating adrenaline you could ever want from Germany’s prized platform. On the interior, the GT is dressed from head to toe in carbon fiber, intricate yellow stitching, and Alcantara leather — reveling in its luxurious pedigree. \n\n</string>
    <string name="ruf">Of the million or so times Faszination on the Nürburgring has been watched online, a ridiculously large proportion are down to my addiction to one of the automotive world’s first viral videos. It shows Ruf test driver Stefan Roser wrestling the original Ruf CTR Yellowbird around the Nürburgring in 1989. With its steering wheel never pointing straight for more than a second, Roser slid, snaked and smoked the 3.4-litre twin-turbo 469bhp CTR around the Nordschleife in a record 8min 5sec, and into legend. Scroll to the very bottom of this article to watch it. \n\n

His roadcraft was flawless. No helmet, no gloves, no five-point harness, no electronic safety net. Just superhuman car control, big balls and the ability to unblinkingly look fear in the eye and tell it to shut the front door. All wrapped up in period-perfect T-shirt, stonewashed jeans, fluffy white socks and a pair of leather slip-ons that never stopped dancing across the pedals. \n\n Alois Ruf – it’s pronounced ‘roof’, not ‘rough’ – is stuck in a meeting, so while we wait the company’s head of sales and marketing, Marc-André Pfeifer, takes me on a tour. We start outside, standing in the kiln-hot Bavarian sunshine, looking up at the imposing house where Alois Ruf’s parents lived.

Using the workshops neighbouring the house, Alois Ruf Snr founded Auto Ruf in 1939. \n\n Post-war, his automotive service and repair business was brisk and, as well as taking on the adjacent fuel station, Ruf Snr built buses. In 1963, infected by his father’s passion for all things automotive, Ruf Jnr took on their first Porsche project – fettling a 356 – and has never looked back. ‘And, 55 years later, we are still a family-owned and family-run business, still producing bespoke Porsche-based cars,’ says Pfeifer, himself in his ninth year at Ruf. ‘Produce’ is the key word here, because just like BMW specialist Alpina, Ruf is recognised under German law as a manufacturer, not just a very good tuner. \n\n

The quality and quantity of that bespoke production becomes apparent when we reach the immaculate workshop and production areas. There are neither CNC machines nor multi-limbed robots here. Instead, there are high-mileage lathes, all manner of metal shearers, panel-beating mallets and personalised trolleys carrying an eclectic array of tools, all worn shiny and smooth with use.

Two rather weary weeping fig trees look out over the modest but pristine garage, no bigger than the size of two tennis courts. Leo Sayer is playing on the stereo. I can see only one computer, its screen displaying a horribly complicated work schedule. Sixteen men work with quiet intensity on the score of cars before them. The air is thick with the aroma of hot metal, oil and alchemy.

</string>
    <string name="rwb">If you’ve gone to enough cars and coffee events or ride nights, you’ve probably seen a lot of the same cars. But go to all of them–or more importantly the right ones–and you might catch a glimpse of a wild looking Porsche 911 wearing the letters “RAUH-Welt” on the top of the windshield. Catch a look at one of those and you are looking at one of the most interesting–and polarizing–Porsches out there. Most of the time said Porsche would be an older 911 (most commonly a 930 generation), sporting a very unique wide-body kit Unlike some tuners that try and make the kit look as seamless as possible, the fenders on these cars often (but not always) have exposes bolts and teams. They typically feature a bold front splitter, and a big rear spoiler. They are almost “meta-Porsches” combining elements form multiple eras of the 911…and they are all the creation of Akira Nakai (also known as Nakai San), and his company, Rauh-Welt Begriff. \n\n The literal translation of the name in German is “Rough-World,” and Begriff means “Concept.” The name is perfectly fitting of these brutal looking 911s. But Nakai didn’t get his start in the world of rear-engined Porsches. Rather, he started in the JDM tuning world of the Toyota AE86. He was a member of the Rough World Drift Crew. Think of the real-world version of Initial D. Nakai would eventually delve into the world of Porsches in the 1990s. A damaged 911 rolled into the body shop he was working in and a bond was formed. At the age of 28, he purchased his first 930 Porsche, and set about tuning it. The results can only be described as sinister. \n\n It is his arguably his most famous work, and it is freaking glorious. Also note the “Stella Atrois” branding on the side. Nakai San is a quirky fellow, and will sit with the cars he’s working on, chain smoking, drinking Stellas, and taking the occasional call on his pink phone. It all just adds to the mysticism of Nakai San. The JDM drift culture influences are apparent, but Nakai San doesn’t see it as merely grafting drift elements onto a Porsche. He views his work as giving the car a soul. Each car gets a unique look; though many get variations of the rivets and large spoiler, others get cleaner fenders and the iconic Porsche “ducktail.” It is that unique touch with has arguably drawn the ire of Porsche purists. You’d be hard-pressed to find a more strict group of traditionalists than that of Porsche. When the Cayenne SUV was announced they all scoffed in disapproval, even though that vehicle allowed Porsche to be successful enough to develop better and better sports cars. Think they’ll like a Japanese chainsmoker hacking up their beloved air-cooled sports cars like a kid strapping M80s to toy soldiers? The vitriol was strong with these folks. \n\n Ever since Nakai San has been around, people have been decrying it as blasphemy. In a sense, they they do have one strong point– there are limited Porsches out there, and as the years go on, there will be less and less air cooled models, thus every time Nakai San gets his hands on one, the number of unmolested old-school 911s goes down. But heres the thing– RWB’s mods are highly visual. There are no major changes to the frame, so if you truly wanted to get your hands on one and restore it back to originality, you could. In that sense, Porsche tuners such as Ruf and Rinspeed are doing more to damage the remaining vehicles, by making deep modifications that cannot be undone if desired. But honestly, I’m inclined to side with the Japanese madman than the stuffy Old Guard, and here’s why. My philosophy on classic cars is that there are a handful of owners who have the resources, the knowledge, and the desire to keep a car completely original. Like a museum piece, these cars cannot be just left in storage–there is constant maintenance even for vehicles that never drive a mile again. \n\n</string>

    <!--    <string-array name="porsches_arry">-->
    <!--    <item>Singer Vehicle Design</item>-->
    <!--    <item>Gemballa Porsche</item>-->
    <!--    <item>RUF automobile GmbH</item>-->
    <!--    <item>RWB / Rauh Welt Begriff</item>-->
    <!--    </string-array>-->
</resources>
